You're debugging for the 4th time.
Claude keeps suggesting the same fix.
Same loop. Same frustration.
What if your AI assistant had a
structured workflow that actually worked?
This is Rune — a 57-skill mesh
that turns your AI coding assistant
from a chatbot into
an engineering team.
It works on Claude Code, Cursor,
Windsurf, and Antigravity.
Let me show you.
Install takes 10 seconds.
claude plugin install rune-kit/rune
57 skills loaded.
For Cursor or Windsurf, one command
compiles all skills into your IDE's format.
npx --yes @rune-kit/rune init
--platform cursor
First thing — let Rune
understand your project.
/rune onboard
Rune scans your codebase, detects
your stack, and creates context files
that persist across sessions.
No more re-explaining your project.
Now let's debug.
Users report login returns 401
for valid credentials.
/rune debug "login returns 401
for valid credentials"
Rune's debug skill traces the code path,
finds the root cause —
an expired JWT secret rotation —
and hands it to fix.
Fix writes the code change.
Verification runs automatically.
Lint pass. Typecheck pass.
Tests pass.
Fixed. Verified. One command.
Now let's build something.
Add Stripe billing to our SaaS app.
/rune cook "add Stripe subscription
billing with plan management"
Cook activates: scout scans the codebase,
detects the @rune/saas extension pack.
Plan creates implementation steps.
See that? Before writing a single line
of code, Rune's adversary skill
red-teams the plan. Found a missing
webhook security check.
Plan updated. User approves.
Test writes failing tests first.
TDD from the start.
Fix implements the code.
Preflight, sentinel, and review
run quality checks in parallel.
8 phases. TDD. Security scan.
Code review.
All orchestrated automatically.
This isn't a list of
independent tools. It's a mesh.
When debug can't find the cause,
it escalates to problem-solver.
When cook hits a wall 3 times,
it pivots to brainstorm.
When sentinel finds a vulnerability,
it blocks the commit.
57 skills. 200+ connections.
They talk to each other
so you don't have to.
Rune is free and open source.
MIT license.
claude plugin install rune-kit/rune
Or for any IDE:
npx --yes @rune-kit/rune init
Less skills. Deeper connections.
Link in description.